Giri Boy has returned!
What just happened to me?
Weird.
I shouldn't be able to get up, right?
Even though I lost the fight,
for some reason I'm having fun!
Joy Boy?
Luffy's Joy Boy?
Is that what Zunisha said?
What is he talking about?
I was starting to worry.
Are you okay, Mr. Pirate?
Luffy!
What?
Is that you, Mr. Straw Hat?
It is him.
Hey!
Straw Hat's up there!
He's still alive!
So Kaido is lying after all?
You're telling me that Ro is really okay?
I'm so happy!
We sacrificed one of our best agents.
And now Kaido is furious.
I still prefer it to the alternative.
We eliminated a risk factor like no other.
Although we can't know for certain
this could have been a true disaster
we must Seize the Gum-Gum fruit for
ages the world government has chased
after it and For ages it has eluded
our grasp what a joke we have allowed
this embarrassment To go on for
generations 800 years to be precise it's
quite vexing it sounds Foolish but
it's almost as if the fruit is trying
to evade us that's not Entirely
implausible Snow type devil fruits can
have a will of their own if that's
so this fruit Would be rather willful
after all its true name bears the title
of a god the Snow human human fruit
Mythical type model
Nika.
From head to toe, his body was as
elastic as rubber itself, they say.
He fought and frolicked as he fancied,
bringing a smile to people wherever he went.
The warrior of liberation, or
as others called him, Nika,
the sun god.
The fruit's awakened power is said to
impart even greater might to its holder,
but what it truly grants is freedom.
Strength as broad as the imagination,
the most ridiculous power in the world,
one that we could not contain.
Komurasaki is Hiyori!
This is a mistake.
I loved Odin too, you know.
Let's rethink this.
Kaido exploited me, but those
days are all behind us now.
So please, pull out this nail.
I can help us both escape.
Who would listen to you now?
You think me a fool?
My father, he kept his promise to you.
He trusted you.
You told him that Kaido would leave,
that you would free the land of Wano.
He spent five years playing the
fool and dancing as you asked.
He never made a single
excuse to his family.
He honored your conditions.
Then he believed that you'd keep
your word and set everyone free.
So he withstood boiling oil for an hour.
He allowed himself to be cooked alive.
He always, always had a smile on his face.
But the whole nation was taken hostage.
And he was carrying that burden
all by himself in silence.
I can't imagine the pain he felt.
What's the matter, Hiyori?
Father, are you okay with
people talking bad about you?
It doesn't bother me one bit.
Why not?
Because I have you, my family. Really?
Then I want to stay with you forever!
You know what?
That Odin was one hell
of a samurai, wasn't he?
As shogun, I can give him a posthumous
award, or perhaps a monument.
I'm the shogun's daughter, Kozuki Hiyori.
When you speak to me, mind your tongue.
Even when I was starving,
even when I was dressed in rags,
I carried with me the honor that
my father brought to our name.
You have never been a
shogun a day in your life.
You're nothing but a
thief and an imposter.
You're a lowly worm and a coward.
And the longer you live your
pathetic excuse of a life,
the more innocent people die.
Please have mercy.
I can't even move.
Don't lay a finger on me.
Revenge is meaningless.
Think of the future.
Killing me is pointless It still
won't get rid of Dock, right?
Lord Orochi
I have failed you, my task?
Contero, is it really you?
Alas, I'm finished, my lord.
Actually, you're just in time!
Why, there's a new stage
for you right before me?
Burn this bitch to death!
Go, my friend, and make it quick.
A woman who endured for 20 years
fails to get her revenge in
the end it's a tragic comedy for
the ages I tell you do you get
it now you're just a relic of
the Kozuki Kyori the chosen the
strong like me we are blessed
with fortune from heaven itself.
No! Stop it!
Why are you coming this way?
Conqueror, you imbecile!
Iori, you have to help me!
The dawn, it will surely come.
The Kozuki clan always
keep their promises.
I can do everything I ever wanted!
Yup, I think I can get back to the fight!
Wow, my heartbeat sure sounds funny!
I can feel it!
This is it!
This is my peak!
All right!
Why is everybody passing out?
Are we getting hit with Conqueror's Haki?
Where's it coming from?
What the hell's going on?
There's something up there...
on the roof!
Commander Kaido!
Is that really Straw Hat?
Oofy!
Monkey-dead muscles! Muscles!
Here we go!
And look!
Straw Hat.
You're alive.
I'm grateful.
Blast Prince!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Ugh!
Ah! Ah!
Ah!
Take this back!
Mummy.
Karoo!
Fifth gear!
My apologies for what
that fool did to you.
I didn't want to win that way.
Not like that.
No problem.
Time to settle this thing.
Well, aren't you full of surprises?
I was certain you had died.
Me too!
All right, seems your rubber power is
affecting things outside of yourself now.
I assume this means your parametheal
powers have reached their awakening,
but your body changed.
It feels like something else.
Almost like you've gone
through a zolan transformation.
It's dark.
Hey, stop eating me!
Muscle... power!
Hey, turn out the lights!
Ha-ha-ha! Woo-hoo!
I'm like a shooting star!
Call me Lucy Satori!
I'm shooting through your body!
Gum-Gum!
What the hell are you doing in there?
What a bastard!
Wait, Kaido?
Why is he flirting like that?
I'm not sure, but he seems
to have put on weight.
Maybe he's trying out a new form.
How the hell is he doing this to me?
My body's not made of rubber.
I sure am having fun.
Oh, I see two lights.
Ten seconds to launch.
Oh!
Ah!
Hey, lift off!
Don't go make a game for a game!
Ah!
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
Oh Yeah I mean
R have
Ann
Lucy?
This time I got an even better idea!
Home combat!
Whoa!
What am I even looking
at right now? That voice.
He sounds just like Luffy.
Wait, you think that thing is Luffy?
I don't know!
All right, I got you now!
Blast red!
Ah!
Diss - Suck him up!
Straw Hat!
Comic-Con!
Conqueror of three!
Wow!
Ragnaraku!
That hurt!
That Straw Hat?
Well, he certainly looks different.
Is this a damn comic strip?
You put on a good show, but it seems all
you're running around wore you out already.
Pity.
Your best isn't enough to beat me.
You think so?
I got plenty left in the tank.
I pooped.
What happened to your face?
Almost forgot.
I was dead.
We're halfway there anyway!
No wonder this wore me out so much.
You can die in peace this time.
The story of the battle you fought
will be passed down for generations.
That's not what I want.
That's stupid.
When you're dead, you're just...
it really is him with those
white clothes in that white hair.
He looked like a different person.
I'm worried he's back.
But his voice is fading away.
It's not over.
Cuz I'm still alive.
We gotta give one of a happy ending right?
Momo right?
For Tama!
For Kin'emon!
For Pedro!
It's time to die.
Is that supposed to scare me?
It wouldn't even be the first time today.
Come on, heart.
Be louder for me.
Now that's more like it.
All right!
This is the beast!
Be careful!
Behind you!
Ah!
Huh?
This is completely insane.
I'm in a conqueror's Haki.
This strange white transformation.
This freedom that seems to be
warping the world around him.
I've never seen anything like that.
Up here, up here, follow me!
You're starting to get it?
Yum, yum, caribou!
Feels like I'm playing
games with a damn kid.
I'm sick of this crap.
Three, two, one.
What?
Yeah!
Oh!
We haven't fun yet, Kaido!
Woohoo!
That was strong!
It was really funny too!
Hmm, I can't make up my mind.
Hey, what should I call that technique?
Gum-Gum something.
Gum-Gum blah.
Are you still, Straw Hat?
Oh, yeah.
That's me.
Oh, Joy Boy.
Joy Boy, how long it's been
since I've felt this rhythm.
Can you hear me, Joy Boy?
It feels as if you're right beside me.
My heart is dancing with excitement.
I cannot help but feel
that fate is at work.
I cannot help but put my
faith in this young man!
You wanna know who I am?
Monkey D.
Luffy, the man who surpasses you,
and then become King of the Pirates!